import { Exercise } from ".";

export const BODY: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "голова",
    "answer": "gołowa",
    "extra": "🧑‍🦱"
  },
  {
    "question": "лицо",
    "answer": "liczo",
    "extra": "😊"
  },
  {
    "question": "глаз",
    "answer": "głaz",
    "extra": "👁️"
  },
  {
    "question": "ухо",
    "answer": "ucho",
    "extra": "👂"
  },
  {
    "question": "нос",
    "answer": "nos",
    "extra": "👃"
  },
  {
    "question": "рот",
    "answer": "rot",
    "extra": "👄"
  },
  {
    "question": "зуб",
    "answer": "zub",
    "extra": "🦷"
  },
  {
    "question": "волосы",
    "answer": "wołosy",
    "extra": "💇"
  },
  {
    "question": "шея",
    "answer": "szeja",
    "extra": "🦴"
  },
  {
    "question": "рука",
    "answer": "ruka",
    "extra": "🤚"
  },
  {
    "question": "кисть",
    "answer": "kiść",
    "extra": "🤲"
  },
  {
    "question": "палец",
    "answer": "palec",
    "extra": "☝️"
  },
  {
    "question": "ноготь",
    "answer": "nogot´",
    "extra": "💅"
  },
  {
    "question": "нога",
    "answer": "noga",
    "extra": "🦵"
  },
  {
    "question": "ступня",
    "answer": "stupnia",
    "extra": "🦶"
  },
  {
    "question": "колено",
    "answer": "kolieno",
    "extra": "🦿"
  },
  {
    "question": "спина",
    "answer": "spina",
    "extra": "💪"
  },
  {
    "question": "плечо",
    "answer": "plieczo",
    "extra": "🦾"
  },
  {
    "question": "грудь",
    "answer": "grud´",
    "extra": "🫀"
  },
  {
    "question": "живот",
    "answer": "żywot",
    "extra": "🫃"
  },
  {
    "question": "сердце",
    "answer": "sierdce",
    "extra": "❤️"
  },
  {
    "question": "мозг",
    "answer": "mozg",
    "extra": "🧠"
  },
  {
    "question": "кость",
    "answer": "kość",
    "extra": "🦴"
  },
  {
    "question": "печень",
    "answer": "piecień",
    "extra": "🫁"
  },
  {
    "question": "горло",
    "answer": "gorło",
    "extra": "🗣️"
  },
  {
    "question": "язык",
    "answer": "jazyk",
    "extra": "👅"
  },
  {
    "question": "желудок",
    "answer": "żiełudok",
    "extra": "🫄"
  },
  {
    "question": "пальцы ног",
    "answer": "pałcy nog",
    "extra": "🦶"
  }
];
